I don't want nobody to get killed
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame where all is spread
Oh, I don't take all of the blame, you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sun, no light, such a mess, I love you
Don't kill your walls, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the changes somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my job
The shadows of the earth can lose you so far
The golden end is so wrong
What I know is the pain that makes us so human after all
You're going to see me unfold, a good show
About your precious worth
This card may respond to your call
And so it begins
Don't let them get away, kill all the vampires
Well, I guess we got the results we were after
Lieutenant Colonel
When this is over, we have a lot to talk about
It'd be smart for you to forget everything you saw here
That's an order
Lieutenant Colonel
Stop right there, miss
Unauthorized access to this area is strictly prohibited
I'm a member of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army's Vampire Extermination Unit
Even if that's true, it doesn't give you clearance
This place is off-limits to anyone ranked company officer or lower
What is the purpose of this facility?
I'm afraid I can't divul-
It's where they run tests on the lab rats
Hey, what are you worried about?
Every soldier in Shinjuku knows about this place
What do you mean by lab rats?
Scientists are doing research on captured vampires
They're looking for weaknesses
So they're experimenting on people here?
I don't think I'd call those monsters people
Please let me in
I want some answers
We told you this place is off-limits
Even if I have this?
The Karagi family
Thank you
Wait
The Karagi family controls the entire Demon Army
Which means you should have a much higher rank than you do
I guess I just like the sound of Sergeant
Besides, I don't have much interest in the silly power struggle over rankings
That's what killed my sister, after all
My sister, the Karagi family calls me
Wait
Oh, God!
So this is where you're hiding.
Damn it. I'm gonna kill those guards.
This won't take long. I have a question.
I've got no answers. Please, see yourself out.
You still hasn't regained consciousness. It's been five days.
What the hell did you do to him?
Or rather, what are you going to do to him, Lieutenant Colonel?
You ordered me to give him a special drug combination because his cursed gear is so strong.
So I gave him these pills just like you asked.
There to blame. The drugs are why he lost control.
I'm right, aren't I? Answer me, Lieutenant Colonel!
It's not like you to wear your emotions on your sleeve.
You must be upset.
What are you hoping I'll say?
That I have no idea what you're talking about?
Or would you feel better if I told you that you're delusional?
Neither! Just tell me the truth about you!
And don't get angry if I mention human experimentation.
Think carefully now.
What would you do to ensure the future of humanity?
How can we survive in this ruined world and kill the four horsemen of John?
More importantly, how do we completely eradicate the vampires?
A human victory will require sacrifice.
Just think how many people died so your older sister, Mahiru Haragi, could complete the cursed gear.
Sacrifice is the only reason we have a fighting chance.
Don't let your feelings for you get in the way of remembering that.
You're blushing, Shinoa.
I don't care what goes on between the two of you privately, but the army's plans for him are not of your concern.
Go away.
But you haven't answered my questions!
I said go!
Go!
That drug wears off in five days.
If you do have feelings for him, then you should stay by his side.
Be there when he opens his eyes.
You, please, you need to wake up.
For me.
I'm not sure, but I think I might be falling for you.
We need your help.
Without you, our squad's incomplete.
Wake up for all of us.
It's time to retreat.
No!
Let go of me!
I'm going to save you!
I know you must be upset, but now's not a good time.
Take a look.
All of his human friends will do absolutely anything to protect him.
No.
Bastards!
Damn those filthy humans!
Yes.
Finally.
You're developing a proper disgust for humanity.
Shut up!
You hate vampires, and now you're learning to hate humans.
I'm curious as to which one you will choose.
I can't wait to find out.
Let's go.
Don't touch me!
My patience wears thin.
You've had enough fun for one day.
Now shut your mouth, nega.
Detoxification of the curse is now complete.
These are the first tears I've shed since becoming a vampire.
I didn't know I could still cry.
Man, I can't believe one measly human caused all that damage.
It's insane.
Mika, from what I saw, it looked like he singled you out.
You're getting good at the silent treatment.
The real issue is what the hell that kid was, and if he's the only one.
I wouldn't want to face an army of them.
The issue's already been raised in the Progenitor Council.
They suspect it's magic that the humans have discovered a forbidden enchantment that could destroy the world.
They called it Seraph of the End, I think.
Word is that our attack on Shinjuku was actually to retrieve the enchantment.
Really?
I guess the mission was a failure.
Who knows?
Lord Fared was in charge.
I never have any idea what's really going on with him.
Sometimes I think he seems happier when we fail.
You probably know more about him than us, Mika.
That deviant always keeps you within arm's reach.
Is that how you wormed your way into Kruel's favor?
Tell us, Hyakuya.
What exactly is your story?
We can always look into your past on our own.
You want my story?
Who I am?
Wait, you are human, right?
Don't tell me that they changed you.
You both must be blind.
Can't you tell by looking at me?
I'm just another ugly vampire.
What does that mean?
Mikaela Hyakuya.
Kruel Tebbish, the third progenitor, requests your presence.
Please proceed to the royal audience chamber at once.
Hear that, Renee?
The queen's tugging on her little pet's leash.
Get a pair.
Take a pair.
You decide to get three of us.
She wants to the muzzle.
Roll the
The queen's tugging.
Toeaso.
Sure.
Here we go.
It's really the queen of theue.
Iron Man.
Though you have to leave
You only can't take her lost.
No over.
hơn nine toär organizes.
I'll say to myself too.
You can't take her touch with you.
So let's lift this.
Do you just try that?
Hey, Yoichi, wake up!
What's going on?
Whoa, you're awake?
This is a miracle!
Why am I in a hospital?
The last thing I remember...
Thank goodness!
Hey, what about that?
Everyone will want to know you're up.
I'll go tell them the news.
Wait, hold on a second.
What happened?
Is everyone okay?
You sound worried.
It's no big deal.
I was just...
Everyone's fine.
You're the only one who we thought might have been a goner.
That's good.
You've actually been in a coma for seven days.
Say what?
Seven days?
I know.
That's why I gotta tell everyone.
That's good.
Nobody got hurt.
What a relief.
Mika, that wasn't just a dream.
I can't believe you're still alive.
All these years, I can't believe it.
Mika.
Now, here's a sight I never expected to see.
You're such a crybaby.
It's understandable.
Of course you're gonna shed some tears.
You just found out your family's alive.
I'm glad you're awake.
We were all really worried after what happened.
I don't know what happened.
It's a blank.
Mika's the last thing that I remember.
You're sure you can't recall anything else?
Nothing.
Interesting.
Well, you said you were sleepy and then you laid down on the battlefield.
Huh?
Are you kidding me?
Of course.
Actually, you were knocked unconscious.
Our squadron was getting flattened.
But then our reinforcements showed up.
The main unit, led by Lieutenant General Kureto and Major General Shinya.
They drove the enemy back.
And what about the vampires?
Did they all get away?
No nobles were captured, but we killed a lot of the normal vampires.
We even took a few of them as prisoners.
Still, we allowed too many of them to escape.
What happened to him?
You want to know about your friend?
Did he escape?
Look, about Mika.
Just come out and say it.
Whether he's my friend or my enemy, I have to know what happened.
If he's alive or not.
So what happened to him when I lost consciousness?
You won't like this.
But he was taken by the vampires.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I understand.
Thanks, Shinoa.
Just keep your cool.
You still need to recover.
So don't even think about going off and raiding the vampire city.
Don't worry.
I'll stay put.
Knowing that Mika's alive is enough for me.
At least for now.
I'm happy to hear that.
I can carry him to safety.
Where can we go to regroup?
Let's get him to the temporary base.
Hurry!
You and Mika, they were family first.
Hey.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Seriously.
Oh.
Of course.
Shinoa.
What are you?
What's this?
Were you injured?
Oh, the bandage.
That's what this is about.
I'm okay now, but one of the vampires took a little sip.
So you're finally awake.
It took you long enough.
What the hell?
What do you think you're doing with him?
Oh, it's not what you think, Mitsu.
I was just explaining to him that a vampire bit me the other day.
Hold up.
You've got a bandage, too?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thanks.
Why don't you use your inside voice?
You're in the hospital.
Who do you think you are?
He looks just fine to me.
Did you enjoy your little nap?
Were you concerned?
Huh?
Why would I waste my valuable time worrying about you, dumbass?
Don't try to act tough.
We all know you were worried.
After all, you spent quite a bit of time sitting by his bed.
What?
Okay, now you're just making stuff up.
I was never in here watching him sleep.
I thought you said not to tell him about watching him sleep.
Shut up.
Hey, listen up, guys.
I want to say something.
What?
Spit it out.
Sure.
Go on.
It's no big.
I just wanted to say thank you, and to apologize for sleeping so long.
You know, I'm lucky to have all of you.
Call a doctor.
He obviously still needs medical attention.
Yep.
He definitely hit his head or something.
I don't think so.
He was actually been a good guy from the beginning.
Well, I hope he hasn't lost his nerve.
He's starting to sound pathetic.
I'm gonna kick all of your asses.
Anyway, we've got plenty of time to rest.
It's good that we get a little downtime to heal.
Hm?
What do you mean?
That's right.
We're on hiatus until you recover.
The Shinawa Hiragi squad is taking a break.
A break, huh?
I know you're probably anxious to go after Mika, but you'll need to regain your strength first.
You're right.
I'll take it easy and behave for the time being.
I don't want to cause any more trouble.
Any requests?
I'm gonna go pick up some drinks for us.
That's our kimizuki.
Always trying to take care of his family.
Never mind.
Wait, I'll come with you.
You only have two hands.
And on the opposite end of the spectrum, we have Mitsu,
who doesn't have a nurturing bone in her body.
Hold it right there.
I don't exactly see you playing Team Mom.
I don't have to because I'm the team leader.
I don't have to because I'm the g różnych one.
I don't have to because I think I hold you hard.
I just want to make this accessible.
Bye.
none of my friends got seriously hurt
Mika is still alive
it's unbelievable
why are so many good things happening to me
he's out there somewhere
and I'll find him again
Mika
you
I'll do whatever it takes
I swear on everything
I'll save you
don't you find it amusing that things seem to be going so smoothly
as usual the humans lust for power is out of control
and we vampires are so arrogant that we take things too lightly
wouldn't you agree with me or does my partner see things differently
you're so serious
here you go
all of our research data
one more thing
I almost forgot
here you go
Thank you.